[
    {
        "prompt": "!",
        "name": "reg1q1",
        "a1": "Period",
        "a2": "End of line",
        "a3": "Any character",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "prompt": "*",
        "name": "reg1q2",
        "a1": "Match any character",
        "a2": "Match preceding character any number of times",
        "a3": "Match any number",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "prompt": ".",
        "name": "reg1q3",
        "a1": "Match any number",
        "a2": "Match any character",
        "a3": "Match any non-printing character",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "prompt": "[0-9]",
        "name": "reg1q4",
        "a1": "Match any number",
        "a2": "Match every number",
        "a3": "Match 0 or 9",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "prompt": "[a-p]",
        "name": "reg1q5",
        "a1": "Match the letters a or p",
        "a2": "Match every letter from a to p",
        "a3": "Ignore the letters a and p",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "prompt": "[a,p]",
        "name": "reg1q6",
        "a1": "Match the letters a or p",
        "a2": "Match every letter from a to p",
        "a3": "Ignore the letters a and p",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "prompt": "[ap]",
        "name": "reg1q7",
        "a1": "Match ap.",
        "a2": "Match a through p",
        "a3": "Capture a through p",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "prompt": "*",
        "name": "reg1q8",
        "a1": "Match preceding element one or more times",
        "a2": "Match preceding element zero or one time",
        "a3": "Match preceding element zero or more times",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "prompt": "\\d",
        "name": "reg1q9",
        "a1": "Match any single non-numerical digit",
        "a2": "Match any single word character",
        "a3": "Match any single numerical digit",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "prompt": "\\D",
        "name": "reg1q10",
        "a1": "Match any single non-numerical digit",
        "a2": "Match any single word character",
        "a3": "Match any single numerical digit",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "prompt": "\\w",
        "name": "reg1q11",
        "a1": "Match any single non-word character",
        "a2": "Match any single word character",
        "a3": "Match any word or non-word character",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "prompt": "\\W",
        "name": "reg1q12",
        "a1": "Match any single non-word character",
        "a2": "Match any single word character",
        "a3": "Match any word or non-word character",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "prompt": "{3}",
        "name": "reg1q13",
        "a1": "Match exactly three times",
        "a2": "Match fewer than three times",
        "a3": "Match three or more times",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "prompt": "a$",
        "name": "reg1q14",
        "a1": "Match a and any character after it",
        "a2": "Match a at the end of a line",
        "a3": "Match uppercase or lowercase a",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 2
    },
     {
        "prompt": "(aaa)",
        "name": "reg1q15",
        "a1": "Capture aaa",
        "a2": "Ignore aaa",
        "a3": "Match aaa",
        "a4": "None of the above.",
        "answer": 1
    }
]
